声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：憨妹 marjorie sealovemoon
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
Walt 让狗安静点
Walt, you gotta keep that dog quiet.
我也不知道它怎么回事
I don't know what's wrong with him.
拜托 Vincent 不要再叫了
Come on, Vincent. Cut that out!
抱歉  抱歉
Hey. Sorry. Sorry.
什么东西?
What is it?
有人在里面
Somebody's in there.
里面的人都已经死了
Everyone in there's dead.
应该是Sawyer
Sawyer.
我在你后面 蠢驴
Right behind you, jackass.
Jack
我用手电筒照照看
I'm gonna shed some light on this thing.
快逃!
Run! Get out of here!
天哪! 怎么办?
crud. Now what?
快!
Come on.
它们走了
They've gone.
什么鬼东西?
What the bloody hell was that?
双字幕： Sealovemoon  marjorie 七色九天
那些野猪是来寻找食物
Those boars were looking to feed.
我们得尽快把尸体处理掉
We have to get rid of the bodies.
埋了?   有一大堆死人呢
Bury them? There's a whole bunch in there.
超过20个
More than 20.
没有铲子很难挖
Digging will be difficult without shovels.
不能埋
Not bury.
我们得把他们烧了
We need to burn them.
他们是"人"
They're people.
我知道他们是人  Kate
I know they're people, Kate.
烧掉他们?!
Burning the remains.
任何方法都比"烧掉他们"要好
They deserve better than that
好什么好  被野兽吃掉就好了?
Better than what? Being eaten by wild animals?
就是因为要发生这样的事
That's what's gonna happen.
我们埋藏的尸体还是会被野兽挖出来吃掉的
Any bodies we bury are not gonna stay buried for long.
我知道这么做很难 但那个太阳底下的半机身...
Look, I know this seems harsh,but that fuselage in the sun...
这不是他们"应该得到"或"不应该得到"的问题
It's not about what they deserve.
他们已经死了  可我们没有
They're gone, and... we're not.
你说的可能有些道理
What you say may be true,
但是若要我们决定以何种方式让他们安息
but for us to decide how these people are laid to rest
我们没这个权力
it's not right.
无视他们的遗愿?
No regard for their wishes?
他们的宗教?
Their religions?
我们没有时间把每个人的宗教信仰搞清楚
We don't have time to sort out everybody's god.
真的吗?  我记得有一句话说我们无疑是由时间组成的
Last I heard, we were positively made of time.
我也很不乐意这么做
I'm not happy about it.
但我们是在偏离航道1000英里的地方坠毁了
We crashed a thousand miles off course.
救援队在另外一个地方找我们
They're looking in the wrong place.
已经过了4天了
It's been four days.
一个人都没来
No one's come.
明天清晨  我要你们每个人开始收集木头
Tomorrow morning we need everyone to start gathering up wood
干草
dried brush.
我们得把那机身烧成一个熔炉
We'll turn that fuselage into a furnace.
等到明天太阳下山以后  我们再点火
Wait until the sun goes down tomorrow night before we set the fire.
如果他这么急着想要焚尸体为什么我们要等到太阳下山?
If he's so eager to burn the bodies, why are we waiting till sundown?
他希望有人会看到这样的求救信号
He's hoping someone will see it.
看起来昨晚并不只我一个没睡好
Looks like I'm not the only one who didn't sleep last night.
比起收集柴火 我有更好的事情要做
There are better things to do with my time than collect firewood.
你不同意Jack的做法
You don't agree with Jack.
你在做什么?
What are you making?
暂时还说不清楚
Too soon to talk about.
我甚至不知道它会不会工作
I'm not sure if it will even work.
你还在试着接收信号  是吧?
Trying to pick up the transmission?
那个我们在接收机里听到的求救信号
The one we heard on the transceiver
如果那个法国女人的求救信号真的被循环播放16年了
If the French woman's transmissions have been playing on a loop for 16 years
那这个岛上一定有电力来源
there must be a power source on the island.
这是很重要的一个线索
A significant one.
你能找到它吗?
And you can find it?
理论上来说  是的
Hypothetically, yes.
我在做一种天线
I'm making an antenna of sorts.
然后把天线安置在岛上的不同位置
With a few of these mounted at different points on the island
或许我可以用接收机来三角定位这个信号
I may be able to triangulate the signal
试着找出这信号是哪儿来的
Find out where it's coming from
那么我能帮上什么忙吗?
So, what can I do to help?
看来你和我一样急着要离开这个岛
It appears you're as anxious to get off this island as I am.
接球 Vincent
Catch the ball, Vincent.
好家伙
Good boy.
接得漂亮  Vincent
Good job, Vincent.
你去哪  小子?
where you going, man?
哪儿都不去
Nowhere.
我只想看看Locke先生在干什么
I just thought I'd see what Mr. Locke was doing.
要不你和爸爸一块儿找柴火去?
why don't you help your dad with the wood?
我敢肯定 Locke先生一定不喜欢一个小孩成天在他周围晃来晃去
I'm sure Mr. Locke doesn't want a kid hanging around him all day.
至少他会和我说话
At least he talks to me.
走  Vincent
Come on, Vincent.
你这人怎么回事?
What's your problem?
-把它们给我!  -要是不呢?
-Hand 'em over!  -How about no?
这儿这么多人  你还想撒野?
There's other people here, or don't you give a crap?
是谁吃的比这每个人的平均分额还多!
If one of us wouldn't eat more than his fair share!
-你这么做太霸道了  -伙计们 好停手了
-That's bull!  -Knock it off.
你是不是占着便宜才会开心...
You're not happy unless you're screwing...
我惹人喜欢  肉球!
Hey, I'm peachy, pork pie!
-伙计 停手了!  -滚开  "地铁"!
-Knock it off!  -Stay out of this,metro!
你俩怎么回事?
What's going on?
Jethro在这儿藏最后一包花生豆
Jethro's hoarding the peanuts.
这是我的  我在那儿找到的
My own stash. I found it in there.
还剩多少食物?
What about the rest of the food?
根本没食物了  伙计
There is no rest of the food, dude.
都.....已经吃光了
We kinda... ate it all.
什么?
What?
好了  请大家冷静
Okay, everybody, just calm down.
我们会找到食物的
We can find food.
这岛上有充足的东西来供我们维持生命
There are plenty of things we can use for sustenance.
那么我们该"怎么"找这些用来维持生命的食物?
And exactly how are we gonna find this sustenance?
打猎
We hunt.
你怎么在飞机上找到这刀的?
How'd you get that knife on the plane?
我托运的
Checked it.
可以说你投的好  也可以说...
You either have very good aim,or
投得不好  Mr...
very bad aim, Mr...
Locke
他的名字是Locke
His name is Locke.
好的  Locke先生  那么我们该打什么猎?
Mr. Locke, what is it that we're hunting?
我们都知道这岛上有野猪
We know there are wild boar on the island.
看它们的长相是尖背野猪
Razorbacks, by the look of them.
昨晚闯进营地的那些是小猪
The ones that came into the camp were piglets.
每只重100至150磅
A hundred, 150 pounds each.
那就意味着附近一定有只母猪
Which means that there's a mother nearby.
重250磅  拱着背  还有獠牙  性情暴戾
A 250-pound rat with scimitar-like tusks and a surly disposition
就喜欢吃周围动物的内脏
who'd love nothing more than to eviscerate anything near.
野猪的常用攻击方式是围着你打转  然后从后面突袭你
A boar's mode of attack is to circle and charge from behind
所以我想 要制服一头野猪  我们至少要3个人
so it will take three to distract her
我从侧面攻击小猪  用刀击中然后割破喉咙
long enough for me to flank a piglet,pin it and slit its throat.
你还把刀还他?
And you gave him his knife back?
是的  除非你能想出更好的点子...
Well, if you've got a better idea...
总比你们3个闯入魔鬼森林要好
Better than three of you wandering into the forest
就用一把小刀制服一只大猪?
to bag a hunk o' ham with nothing but a little bitty hunting knife?
明摆着不可能  这是我听过的“最好”的主意
Hell, no.It's the best idea I ever heard.
这家伙是谁?
Who is this guy?
Locke上校  这条线安全吗?
Colonel, is this line secure?
安全  GL 12 说吧
Line secure. GL-12, go ahead.
目标地点已获悉
Target area is acquired.
1300小时后 军事演戏开始 重复一遍 我们已准备好行动
Maneuvers are a go for 1300 hours. Repeat: We are a go.
收到 我们将在1300小时后在指定地点集合
Roger that. We'll convene at the usual rendezvous point at 1300 hours.
Locke! 我告诉过你要把TPS报告在今天中午之前准备好
Locke! I told you I need those TPS reports done by noon today.
不是12:30  不是12:15  就中午
Not 12:30, not 12:15. Noon.
你才第一次跟我说  Randy
I heard you the first time, Randy.
上班时间不准打私人电话  少校
And no personal calls during office hours, colonel.
那么...
So...
准备好捕野猪了  恩?
...hunting boar now, huh?
谁说这是我第一次捕野猪?
Who says this is my first time boar hunting?
告诉我
Tell me
为什么我们一旦要深入到丛林内部  你就一定跟来?
how come anytime there's a hike into the heart of darkness, you sign up?
里面有什么  你知道的!!
You know what's in there.
事实是  我不知道...
Actually, I don't.
你也不知道
And neither do you.
你对我们的新朋友感觉怎么样?
What's your feel on our new friend?
他看起来很清楚自己在干什么
He seems to know what he's doing.
你可以说我多虑  但一个扛着一整箱刀子的人...
Call me paranoid, but anyone who packs a suitcase full of knives...
可能是我不知情
If I didn't know any better
我想你是在担心我  Jack
I'd say you're worried about me.
可能我也不知情
If I didn't know better
我想说  你是不是不能在一个地方呆的久一点 Kate
I'd say you have a problem staying in one place.
所以  告诉我 为什么你也去?
You wanna tell me why you're really going?
Sayid给了我这个 然后他就能三角定位我们接收过的那个求救信号
Sayid gave me this so he can triangulate the distress signal we heard.
找出信号发射地
Find the source.
这和野猪无关?
This isn't about boars?
我是素食者
I'm a vegetarian.
为什么我不能去?
But why can't I come?
因为我说了不能去
Cause I said so.
瞧 我...
Look
要离开...
I am going off away to
去打猎
hunt
并且 呃...
and
我在想你是否...
I was wondering if you...
呃  是否能
if you
照看我的孩子
you could keep an eye on my boy
这是Walt
Walt
我是Michael
And I'm Michael.
不管怎么说  你能帮我照管孩子吗
Anyway, could you watch him for me
直到我回来?
until I come back?
抱歉  我听不懂  但你答应了  是吗?
Sorry, I don't understand, but you're cool with this, right?
我不要临时保姆
I don't need a baby-sitter
拜托  Vincent需要你呆在这儿
Come on, man. Vincent needs you here.
嘿  开心一点
Hey, cheer up.
对我来说这是个可以更好的了解你的朋友Locke先生的好机会
This will give me a chance to get to know your friend Mr. Locke.
不管你说什么  是的
Yeah. Whatever.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我是Jack
It's Jack.
-Claire 对吧?  -是的
-Claire, right?  -Yeah.
-(孩子)怎么样...  -哦 他很好 谢谢
-How's the...?  -Oh, he's good.Yeah. Thanks.
我想你应该看看这个
I thought maybe you should see this.
有人在那儿找到的
Someone found it in there.
他们正在收集所有的物品
They're collecting all the belongings.
Steve和Kristen  他们正在讨论结婚事宜
They're wedding plans for Steve and Kristen.
飞机上  他们就坐在我身后的几排
They were on the plane sitting a couple of rows behind me.
我还记得他们  是因为他们看起来开心极了
I remember because they looked so happy.
我不明白Claire 我不知道该怎么做
I don't understand what I'm supposed to do with this.
我们当中一些人在想  是否应该...
well, some of us were wondering if maybe we should
搞个悼念仪式或其它什么的
do some kind of memorial service or something.
你可以做个指导
You could lead it.
-不 我不认为...  -你知道 说几句话就行了
-No, I don't think...  -Well, you know, just a few words
或者直接念一下护照或者驾照上的名字也行...
or even we could just read off names from passports and driver's...
听着  这不是我份内的事
Look, it's not my thing.
好吧
okay.
那我来做吧
Maybe I'll do it.
好的  主意不错 大家想干什么 干什么
Yeah. Sounds fine.Whatever everybody wants.
那个女的还坐在那儿
That woman is still sitting there.
-她丈夫也在飞机上  -好
-Her husband was on the plane.  -Great.
你在听我说话吗?
Are you listening to me?
来个四字短语怎么样: 我不在乎?
What's a four-letter word for "I don't care"?
我在想 最好有个人过去和她说说话
I think somebody should talk to her.
我提拔你去 "America"船长
I nominate you, Captain America
你就不能帮帮自己?
You just can't help yourself,can you?
不能  至少
Yeah, well, at least
在我的照顾下  你不用担心饿着肚子
You don't have to worry about starving with me taking care of you.
我才不会饿着肚子
I'm not gonna starve.
好吧  那你吃什么?
Right. What are you gonna eat?
海里面全是鱼
Ocean's full of fish.
跟你说也是白说
Hate to break it to you.
大海是不会买你的帐的
The ocean is not gonna take your gold card.
你真的认为我一条鱼都抓不到?
You really don't think I can catch a fish?
找到什么了吗?
You find something?
这地已经被猪鼻子拱过了
The ground here has been rooted up.
这就是野猪食物的主要来源: 挖掘
That's how boars get the majority of their food. They dig.
然后  他们会把食物放在地上磨滚对着树反复摩擦
Afterwards, they generally wallow in the dirt and rub up against the trees,
最后用獠牙取出食物
scoring it with their tusks.
好的
Okay.
那么你是什么意思?
So, what's all that mean?
意味着我们离野猪不远了
It means we're close.
-Shannon 对吧?  -是的
-Shannon, right?  -Yeah.
你在做什么吗?
Are you doing anything?
我? 不 我只是 呃... 你在做什么?
Me? No, I was just...What are you doing?
我只是随便逛逛
I was just gonna go for a walk.
-想一块儿来吗?  -哦 好的 当然
-You want to come?  -Yeah. Yes.Sure.
我能问你个问题吗?
Can I ask you something?
我在想你什么时候能爬上来(乐队的地位提升)
I wondered when this was gonna come up.
-是的 我在乐队里是个低音吉他手....  -你知道怎么钓鱼吗?
-Yes, I am the bass guitarist in... -Do you know anything about fishing?
什么? 钓...钓鱼?
What? Fishing?
我祖父曾带我出去他把他知道的都教给了我
My granddad used to take me out.Taught me everything he knows.
教给我他知道的每件事他现在已经去世了 上帝保佑他
Everything he knew.He's dead now, God rest his soul.
是的  我就像一个 ...一个钓鱼能手
Yeah, I'm like a...I'm a fishing fiend.
你知道  我意思是 英国是个岛国
You know,I mean, England's an island
我甩出线就可以钓鱼
so I just throw it in and fish.
很好
Good.
医生  你有空吗?
doc, you got a second?
那位女士一个人坐那儿很久了
That woman's been sitting over there by herself.
或许她在不停的思念她的丈夫
Maybe she's having trouble dealing with her husband.
我想她已经很久没吃过或喝过东西了
I don't think she's had anything to eat or drink.
或许你可以过去和她谈谈?
Think maybe you could go talk to her?
干吗要我过去? 我不是精神科医生 你去吧...
Why me? I'm not a psychiatrist.Maybe you should...
我以为你会想要这么做
Just thought you might want to do it.
是你救了她的命
You're the one that saved her life.
Rose  对吧?
Rose, right?
23A座位的  我是...
Seat 23A. I was...
飞机遇上气流时 我是那个叫你不要担心的家伙
the guy that told you not to worry about the turbulence.
大家都很担心你  Rose
Everybody's getting pretty worried about you, Rose.
如果你喜欢独处  可以
You want to be alone, fine
但你得照顾好自己
but take care of yourself.
你真的应该喝点水
You should really drink.
好吧
Okay.
我们不一定要说话
We don't have to talk.
就这样坐一会儿也行
Let's just sit... for a while.
你儿子...他怎么看待这件事?
How's your son?How's he handling all this?
他比我更好过
A hell of a lot better than I am.
你一定很骄傲  他是个勇敢的孩子
You must be proud.He's a brave kid.
是的  但这不是我的功劳
Yeah. I can't take credit for that.
他的生活中一直没有我
I wasn't part of his life
直到两周前他妈妈过世
till his mother passed away two weeks ago.
-我很抱歉 我还不知道  -没事
-I'm sorry. I didn't know.  -That's okay.
过去的几年 他们一直住在悉尼
They were living in Sydney the past couple of years.
上周我飞过去...
I flew out last week
接他们
to go get him.
你在澳大利亚干什么?
What were you doing?
嘘!
Shh.
讨厌你老是用手指  点来点去
quit giving us the steal signal.
糟透了
It's bad.
行动
Move.
你得行动  少校
You've got to move, colonel.
你的部队正在穿越敌线
Your troops are across enemy lines.
忍耐
Patience
你最缺乏的一种品质
a quality which you lack
是作为一个领导者的必要品质 GL 12
is the hallmark of a leader.GL-12
必要品质?
Hallmark?
多给我讲些领导的事,Locke.
Tell me more about being a leader, Locke.
讲的同时
And while you're at it
顺便跟我说说"少校"的事
tell me about this colonel thing
在人事资源部 我仔细看过你的简历
I perused your file in Human Resources.
你从没参加过什么军队
You've never been in any of the armed forces.
我在玩游戏  Randy
I'm just playing a game, Randy.
这是我的午休时间   我可以玩游戏
It's my lunch hour.I can play a game.
是的
Yeah.
告诉我  什么是"徒步旅行"?
Tell me, what's a walkabout?
经历所谓澳大利亚内地的梦幻之旅
"Experience the dream journeys of the fabled Australian outback."
你没有权力在我桌子上拿东西
You have no right taking that off my desk.
还有你们四处打猎 寻找食物 对吧?
So you wander around hunting and gathering food, right?
徒步?
On foot?
你是不会明白的
Not that you would understand
徒步旅行是一种精神再生的旅行
but a walkabout is a journey of spiritual renewal
人可以从大地得到力量
where one derives strength
从而和大地变得不可分离
from the earth and becomes inseparable from it.
我有假期
I have vacation days.
我要去  Randy  我已经预定好了
I'm going, Randy.I already made a reservation.
John  你真的要做?
Wow, John,you're really doing it?
你告诉Helen了吗?
You tell Helen yet?
是谁  Locke?
What's this, Locke?
你生命中不是有个女人了吗?
You've got a woman in your life.
这不关你的事
None of your business.
你怎么回事  Locke?  你干吗折磨你自己?
What is it with you, Locke?Why do you torture yourself?
我意思是 把自己想象成一个猎手? 一个徒步旅行者?
I mean, imagining you're some hunter?And walkabouts?
醒醒吧  你什么都干不了的
Wake up.You can't do any of that.
Norman Croucher
什么?  Norman什么?
What? Norman what?
Norman Croucher    Norman Croucher
截肢者  没有腿
Double amputee, no legs.
他爬上了史上最高山
He climbed to the top of Mount Everest.
为什么?  命运决定的
Why? It was his destiny.
那就是你所谓的收获  老头?
That's what you think you got, old man?
命运?
Destiny?
只是...
Just...
不要再跟我说  我做不了什么...
don't tell me what I can't do...
John!  他受伤了
John. He's hurt.
John  你听到我说话了吗?
John? Can you hear me?
Locke!
John 你没事吧?
John, you okay?
Locke?
我没事  我没事
I'm fine.
我很好 Helen  风把我吹倒了 就这样
I'm fine, Helen. I just got the wind knocked out of me is all.
Helen?
是吗?
Did I?
那野猪往哪个方向去了?
Which way'd that boar go?
Michael受伤了
Michael's hurt.
我们得把他带回营地去
We have to get him back to camp.
好的 你把他带回营地  我去追野猪
Yeah, you take him back to camp.I'm gonna get that boar.
你说什么呀?
What are you talking about?
我没事 我能做到
I'm fine. I can do this.
John 你不能去
John, you can't.
不要再跟我说 我做不了什么
Don't tell me what I can't do.
抓到了?
Get it?
伙计...
Dude
不要再这么问了
quit asking me that.
抱歉
Sorry.
是你说  你知道怎么抓鱼的!!
It's just you said you knew how to fish.
是的  我曾和老爸去Santa Monica码头
Yeah, off the Santa Monica Pier with my old man
带上一根鱼竿  一些饵
and a fishing pole and bait.
不要指望用尖棒戳到鱼
Never had to try to poke one with a sharp stick.
真的很感激你帮我  谢谢
Well... really appreciate you helping me out. Thanks.
只要让我远离那机身就行
Hey...anything that keeps me away from that fuselage.
抓住那个该死的红脖子蠢蛋
And that freakin' redneck jerk!
妈的! 我真是垃圾! 垃圾! 臭婊...
Damn it! Crap! Crap! Son of a...
你让我试试?
You want me to have a go?
小心点
Knock yourself out.
好吧
All right.
好的  这儿有一条
Okay, here comes one.
集中力量
Put your weight into it.
放松  等候
Easy. Wait for it.
快!
Now!
伙计  你得扎中
Dude, you got to try to pin it.
你看  我差点就抓到了?
Did you see how close I was?
你说的  别为难它
You said not to corner it.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
-你叫Sayid 对吧?  -是的
-Your name's Sayid, right?  -Yes.
我刚找到这个  上面有你的名字
I found this.It's got your name on it.
我还以为没了
I thought I'd lost this.
-谢谢  -不客气
-Thank you.  -Sure.
他的手指会肿胀
His fingers swell.
什么?
Sorry?
Bernard  我的丈夫
Bernard. My husband.
我们一上飞机  他的手指就肿胀
His hands swell up whenever we fly.
海拔的缘故
The altitude.
所以一旦我们乘飞机旅行他就叫我拿着他的结婚戒指
He started having me hold on to his wedding ring whenever we took a plane trip.
我总是把它带在脖子上 怕弄丢了
I always wore it around my neck for safekeeping
直到飞机着陆
just until we landed.
我要你知道  医生  你不必兑现承诺的!
You know, doctor, you don't have to keep your promise.
在飞机上你给我的承诺.....
The one you made me on the plane
说给我作个伴  直到我丈夫从洗手间出来?
to keep me company until my husband got back from the restroom?
我允许你从这个困扰中走出去
I'm letting you off the hook.
你不能这么轻易的甩掉我
Well, you're not gonna get rid of me that easily.
Rose  你不应该一个人呆在这儿
Rose, you shouldn't be out here alone.
你刚遭受过猛烈的冲击
You're suffering from post-traumatic shock.
我们不是都遭受了吗?
Aren't we all?
是的  我们都遭受了
Yeah, I guess we are.
你人很好
You have a nice way about you.
有颗好的心灵
A good soul.
有耐心  关爱他人
Patient, caring.
我想这就是你为什么成为了医生
I suppose that's why you became a doctor.
谢谢  但是...
Thanks, but...
事实是  这和祖传有关
I was just kinda born into it.
家族事业
Family business.
我从没感受过 我这么有活力
I have never felt so alive.
终于告诉了Randy我要离开 真的是...
Getting to finally tell Randy off was...
... 生命的变迁
...life-changing.
我说真的
I mean it.
现在我可以自由自在的做我想做的事
Now I'm free to do all those things I ever wanted to do,
做我命中注定要做的事
things that I know I was destined to do,
就像我们讨论过的那样  Helen
like we talked about, Helen.
太棒了 John  我真替你高兴
It's wonderful, John. I'm happy for you. Really.
我还没告诉你最精彩的部分
I haven't even told you the best part.
你还记得那个...
Do you remember the...
真实的原始徒步旅行吗?
...authentic aboriginal walkabout?
当然  你说了好几周了
Sure. That's all you've talked about for weeks.
是的   我打算去尝试
Yeah, well, I'm gonna do it.
这周末  我要飞往澳大利亚
I'm flying to Australia at the end of the week.
而且我已经 ...
And I've...
我买了两张票子
I bought two tickets.
Helen?
-John 我们已经谈过了  -是的 我知道
-John, we've talked about this.  -Yeah. I know.
我喜欢你  我也喜欢过去的几个月里和你谈论的这些事情
I like you. I've enjoyed talking these past months.
我也是  8个月了
So have I. Eight months
我不允许去见顾客
I'm not allowed to meet customers.
顾客?
A customer?
对你...
Is...?
对你来说  我就是个顾客而已?
Is that what I am to you?
这非比寻常  我是说  这不是我要做的
This isn't really normal. I mean, it isn't what I do.
或许你应该找一个...我说不清楚...治疗师?!
Maybe you should find a, I don't know, therapist.
-我有一个治疗师了  -John...
-I have a therapist.  -John...
我还以为你会明白的  Helen
I thought you understood.
你了解我  比任何人都清楚
You know me better than anyone.
John  如果我们再接着谈的话
If we talk longer
你得多付一个小时的钱了
I'm gonna charge you for another hour
又要89.95美圆
That's another $89.95.
听着 我才不在乎钱!我只是...
I don't care about the money! I just...
我很抱歉 John  我得走了
I'm sorry, John. I got to go.
Helen! Helen!
等等
wait a minute.
在这休息会儿
Just rest here for a minute.
那个瘸腿的家伙应该给我们安排好休息地
I thought the guy with the gimpy leg should be deciding when we rest.
你做什么?
Hey, what are you doing?
试着调测一下信号
Trying to boost the transceiver signal.
我得爬上树去
I'm gonna climb this tree...
把天线安置在那儿
...and attach an antenna.
-你要爬这个?  -是的
-You're gonna climb that?   -Yeah.
别担心
Don't worry.
爬树对你不好
Climbed a lot worse.
Locke
这些是...
These were...
前些天我找到的  当时我在...
I found these the other day when I was...
不管了  收下就是了
Hell, just take it.
谢谢
Thank you.
什么...那是什么?
What is that?
我懂了  牙膏一样的东西
I get it.It's like toothpaste.
爸爸!
Dad!
发生什么事了?
So, like, what happened out there?
爸爸!
Dad!
你的腿看起来糟透了  痛吗?
Your leg's messed up. Does it hurt?
没事儿  没看起来那么糟
It's okay. Not as bad as it looks
勇猛的女猎手回来了
The mighty huntress returns.
-晚餐吃什么 宝贝儿?  -还没到时候
-What's for dinner, honey?  -Not now.
这么说你和野猪打架喽?
It was a boar fight?
算不上打架  是蹂躏啦
Not so much a fight.
就像我被它狼吞虎咽
It was more, you know, like me getting gored.
那...Locke先生在哪?
So, where's Mr. Locke?
我觉得打猎进展的并不顺利
I don't think the hunt went well.
那个光头佬还没回来
That bald guy never came back.
他们什么食物都没带回来?
They didn't bring back any food?
你听到我说什么了吗?
Did you hear what I said?
很可能有人死在那儿不回来了
Somebody might have died.
是的  但是如果他们不做些什么  我们都会死的
We'll die if somebody doesn't do something.
给你
There you are.
我保证过的
As promised
今晚你和我将有一顿丰盛的海鲜大餐
you and I will be dining on fresh catch of the day.
老天!
My fish!
希望你不会介意我把鱼弄成这样吧
Hope you don't mind alfresco.
是的  这不成问题
It was no problem.
你知道吗?  事实上 这鱼花了我好大力气啊
That one gave me a hell of a tussle
但你知道  你必须知道鱼在想什么?
but you have to get inside the mind of the fish.
-我不相信  -我呆在浅水处  把它逼到角落
-I don't believe you.  -I cornered it.
又怎么了?  不忍看到我自力更生啊?
What's the matter? Can't stand to see me fending for myself?
-对这件事 我真的感到很抱歉  -没事
-I am so sorry about this. Seriously.  -It's okay.
-你向他倒什么歉?  -替你道歉
-What are you apologizing for?  -For you
为你像摆弄别人一样摆弄他道歉
For using this poor guy.
随你怎么说
Oh, whatever.
你脑子里错乱的某根神经
In your twisted brain
你认为 这证明你可以照顾你自己了
you think this proves.you can take care of yourself.
我告诉过我会抓到一条鱼 不是吗?
I told you I'd catch a fish, didn't I?
这是很低贱的行为 Shannon  对你来说也是
That's low, even for you.
去救幼鸟或其它什么吧
Oh, go rescue a baby bird or something.
Rose  太阳下山后
Rose, after the sun goes down,
我们将烧掉机身
we're gonna burn the fuselage.
这是我们必须得做的
It's just something that we have to do.
然后我们会在营地搞个悼念仪式
There's gonna be a memorial service back at the camp for those...
为那些没有活下来的人
...for those who didn't make it
向他们告别
for everyone to say goodbye
今晚我会去的
I'd like to be there for that.
你知道  或许你想对你的丈夫说些什么
Maybe if you wanted to say something,You know, about your husband.
什么?
What?
我说  如果你想对Bernard说再见的话
I'm saying, if you wanted to say goodbye to Bernard.
医生  我丈夫没死
Doctor, my husband is not dead.
Rose  他是在飞机的尾舱
Rose, he was in the tail section of the plane.
飞行的时候尾舱折断了
It broke off in mid-flight.
很抱歉  只是那半节机身里的人都不见了
I'm sorry, but everyone who was in the rear of the plane is gone.
他们很可能也在想"我们都已经死了"
They're probably thinking the same thing about us.
医生?
Doctor?
一块去吗?
You coming?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我想我本应该向你保证的
Guess I should have gotten the warranty.
我还会再试一次
I suppose I'll just try again.
当然  我已经没有焊锡了
Of course, I have no welding iron
没有锍钉
no rivets
没有绞线
scorched wiring
看来我还得对....
and it seems I must continue to
每个问我在干什么的人撒谎
lie to anyone who asks me what I'm actually doing!
Sayid...
我们再试一次
We'll try it again.
Kate!
你是不是要说"我告诉过你别去的"?
Is this when you say "I told you so"?
不 我才不会这么浇冷水
No. I'm not big on rubbing it in.
Locke ...
Locke不见了
Locke's gone.
那东西  朝他冲去
That thing,it was moving in his direction.
马上就要烧机身了
Fuselage is ready to go.
有些人决定...
Some of the others decided...
我想烧的时候会有些悼词
I guess there's gonna be some words said over the fire.
-这很好  -还有念名字  我想
-That's good.  -Names read, I think.
我想他们还没准备好  听我们讲一些....
I don't think they're ready to hear about some things...
Jack?
Locke
来自德克萨斯 丹顿的Judith Martha Wexler
Judith Martha Wexler from Denton, Texas.
估计她是去转机
I guess she was gonna catch a connecting flight.
她戴矫正眼镜
She wore corrective lenses
她还是个器官捐赠者
and she was an organ donor.
至少她曾经是
Or at least would have been.
Steve和Kristen
Steve and Kristen.
我不知道他们的姓 但是 ...
I don't know their last name, but...
他们真的很相爱 并且马上就要结婚了
they were really in love and were gonna be married.
不管他们现在在哪
At least wherever they are now
他们已经不再孤独
they're not alone
看起来  他很少旅行
Looks like he hadn't traveled much
至少从护照上看得出来
as far as I can tell from his passport.
看到Jack了吗?
You seen Jack?
干的漂亮
Nice work.
什么?
What?
你知道的 干得很漂亮
Nice work, you know.
刚还在想  我该为你说些什么
Just thought I should say something.
所以  那东西...那 ...
So, that thing... the...
怪物  或其它什么...
...monster, whatever
她说它朝你冲过去
she said it was headed right towards you.
看到了吗?
Get any kind of look at it?
没有
No.
我们安排的徒步旅行
The walkabouts we arrange
不只是一种像散步穿过公园那么简单
here are not just some stroll through the park.
这是一种长途跋涉  得穿越广阔无垠的沙漠
It's trekking across stretches of desert
渡过激流横飞  险象环生的河流
rafting treacherous waters...
你根本不知道你在和什么样的人说话
You've got no idea who you're talking to.
我很清楚我要做的  相信我
I'm well aware of what's involved, believe me.
关于徒步旅行  很可能我知道的比你还多
I probably know more than you.
即使是对一个身强力壮的人来说  这都是一种严酷的考验
It's a trying ordeal for someone in peak physical condition.
听着  我一个月前就预定了这次旅行
I booked this tour a month ago.
我已经付了钱  现在你得在车子上给我留个位置
You've got my money.I demand a place.
你误导了大家
You misrepresented yourself.
-我从没撒过谎  -你疏忽了 Locke先生
-I never lied.  -By omission. Mr. Locke.
你漏了告诉我们你的身体状况
You neglected to tell us about your condition.
我的身体状况不成问题
My condition is not an issue.
四年来我的身体状况都这样
I've lived with it for four years.
这从来没妨碍过我做任何事
Never kept me from doing anything.
不幸的是  对保险公司来说  这就是个问题
Unfortunately, it is an issue for our insurance company.
我不能再让汽车等下去了  这对别人很不公平...
I can't keep the bus waiting.It isn't fair...
不要跟我讲"公平"!
Don't talk to me about fair!
我们承担你飞回悉尼的费用
I'll get you on a plane to Sydney on our dime.
不  我不想回悉尼
No, I don't want to go back to Sydney.
听着  我为这次"徒步旅行"准备好几年了
Look, I've been preparing for this for years.
你只要现在让我进汽车就行  我能做到!
Just put me on the bus right now.I can do this!
不  你不能
No, you can't.
你不要走
don't you
你不知道你干了些什么!
You don't know who you're dealing with!
不要再跟我说  什么我做不了 永远都不要!
Don't ever tell me what I can't do!
这就是命运
This is destiny.
这就是我的命运
This is my destiny.
听着  我本来可以做的 妈的!!!
Listen, I'm supposed to do this, damn it!
不要再跟我说  什么我做不了!
Don't tell me what I can't do!
不要再跟我说 我不能...
Don't tell me what I can't...
你!  快!  过来!
You! Come on!Come over here!
过来!  快!
Get over here! Give me a hand!
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====